ALL PERSONS, LOCATIONS, RELIGIONS,
INCIDENTS, AND ORGANIZATIONS IN THIS DRAMA
ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS HAVE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER PARENTAL SUPERVISION
SCENES INVOLVING ANIMALS WERE FILMED
SAFELY WITH EXPERT ADVICE AND COOPERATION
TIN CAN BASTARD
The offer for your return to directing
still stands.
I'll wait for your call.
Just give me a week.
I can secure
all of last year's quarterly data.
Deok-sun?
Yes.
The Haemado guesthouse owner's niece.
The teen who looks like Ssuk?
Yes.
- Wait.
You met again at work?
She's been working there for a while.
She joined our team last week.
Is she pretty?
What? She's younger than Wan-do.
Even back then, she wasn't exactly normal.
Early winter weather is setting in.
But she grew up…
to be quite a brat.
Must've been nice to see her.
You talked about her sometimes.
Officials say that in the early hours
of the 24th or 25th,
rain will fall nationwide,
dropping temperatures,
and potentially turning into snow.
This year, Seoul's first snow is expected
to arrive 11 days earlier than last year.
We hope Seoul
will see its first snow very soon.
Where should we watch it?
The playground?
We haven't been in a while.
Sure, let's do it.
4. ARE WE DREAMING THE SAME DREAM?
No way! Is it really Park Yong-dae?
The athlete?
He has that dragon tattoo.
It's him without a doubt.
An article revealed his initials.
Did you see the article?
- Hey.
Someone posted that online a week ago,
and it went viral.
Park Yong-dae is known for this.
That's why he got divorced.
- I knew it.
At the scene of last week's motel fire,
an ex-international turned K League coach…
I'll be out of touch for a while.
SU-YEON
I'LL BE OUT OF TOUCH FOR A WHILE
…was confirmed to have been
with a same-sex partner,
causing a stir in the sports world.
The K League and Mr. P…
I'm not mad. Call me.
…have not released
an official statement yet.
The industry is reportedly
considering legal action.
HIDING WON'T SOLVE ANYTHING
Human rights organizations say
this case highlights
public figures' privacy issues
and discrimination
based on sexual orientation,
and argued for better protection
of their human rights…
Is that Park Yong-dae?
FERRY TERMINAL
TICKETS
…and respect for diversity.
Hey!
Wait up.
Come on, wait for me!
Your aunt will meet you there.
Jeez.
Hey.
Take this.
Your feet always get cold.
You need your bed socks.
Mr. Lee from Handel Piano Academy.
The second son of Pastor Kwon
from New Hope Church.
The husband of Lucky Hair Salon's owner.
The police officer
who lived in Daehu Apartments.
Did you think I didn't know?
I've known everything since I was nine.
Look, Su-a--
But Dad.
How could you do it with my friend's dad?
I did it.
I'm the one who posted it online.
I hope everyone criticizes you.
NO INTERNET SERVICE
HAEMADO GUESTHOUSE
HERO FROM HAEMADO
NATIONAL TEAM SOCCER PLAYER PARK YONG-DAE
HAEMADO
HERO FROM HAEMADO
NATIONAL TEAM SOCCER PLAYER PARK YONG-DAE
Excuse me.
Which way is the bus stop?
Hang this up first.
All right.
- Wow, it's big.
Wow.
- Here, grab this.
Nice.
- Looks great.
Here.
- That'll do.
Looks like he ran away here
because he caused trouble on the mainland.
What trouble?
Maybe he's the one
who ruined the mural at the dock.
He's the only outsider here.
According to Mr. Kim from the store,
he's really good at hwatu.
Really?
- Yes.
I wonder what kind of trouble he caused.
Exactly.
Maybe he was playing hwatu and--
- No way.
Oh dear.
I got dumped by a girl.
- Oh!
I got dumped by a girl
I liked for ten years,
so I ran away.
Ran away?
- Ran away?
Yes, it hurt too much to keep seeing her.
So I ran as far away as possible.
First, a month in Chungju,
then Daejeon,
Suncheon, Namwon, and Boseong.
And before I knew it,
I made it to the edge of the land.
Back to work.
Right.
- Oh my.
My, my.
- Grab here.
Gosh.
- Grab it.
Oh my.
How long is she going to
be like that, anyway?
Connect the TV.
I need to watch the news.
I said no.
Stop.
It's not because of Dad.
I need to prepare my article portfolio
for the youth journalism contest
in September.
Hey, Deok-sun.
Your aunt is doing this
because she's worried about you.
Your father, Yong-dae, told us
not to let you watch the news.
He practically begged us.
He deserves to be criticized
for disgracing the national uniform.
Goodness!
- My dad is just paying the price
for his negative impact on society.
That little--
- Oh, no.
Calm down.
- Calm down.
Are you not going to turn it on?
Fine, I'll take care of it.
Hey!
- That brat.
Oh my goodness.
I'll make you eat seaweed soup
so you lose the contest!
You're dead meat!
We also can't watch TV because of her.
Get to work.
Get over here!
How upsetting.
Damn it.
Oh!
SU-YEON
DAD
I lied.
I didn't post it.
What?
Please.
This is so annoying.
What are you doing?
How long have you been there?
Since you started bawling like, "Waah!"
I don't cry like that.
If you say so.
What, you want one?
I'm in high school. That's bad.
What you did to your dad's mural is bad.
This is just…
a 225-won comfort.
Let me have one.
That 225-won comfort.
Hey, Deok-sun.
Look at you now.
What are you doing? Sit.
It was funny
how you pretended not to know me,
so I played along.
But you never stopped pretending.
Were you going to keep pretending?
Yes.
- "Yes"?
A lot of time has passed,
and the workplace is a professional space.
And more importantly,
since we were never that close anyway,
I didn't think
there was any need to acknowledge you.
Then you should've kept it up.
Why did you suddenly show up?
I needed the sample processing date.
And back then,
I didn't know
you were a selfish bystander.
"A bystander"?
- Let me ask you something.
Why I got in Mr. Oh's truck,
and why my sudden interest
in the sweet potatoes?
Is that what you want to know?
How many quarterly
subcontractor goods receipts do you have?
I've secured up to the third quarter.
Secure all of last year's first.
Eat up.
Traffic will be bad later.
We can't make any stops.
I'm so sorry.
I thought it was all discarded.
Why do something different for no reason?
This wouldn't have happened
with our usual supplier.
He was just trying his best
to lower the unit cost.
Why did he need to try?
No one cares anyway.
But there were no issues
with the vacuum sealing during testing.
They probably ran it
with the laminated film spec then,
but changed it for production.
Why let yourself get ripped off like that?
He started when you did, right?
Anyway, try not to stand out or act up.
Especially you, Gung.
Don't get cocky, got it?
Of course,
I'll listen to your expert advice.
I won't forget.
Why, you little…
I have plans. Have lunch without me.
Oh, take Ms. Park Su-a with you.
Take her.
- I will.
Why doesn't he take her?
Eat up, Yeon-ju.
Fill yourself.
Just spit it out.
After I see you eat
ten pieces of meat first.
I'm not that antisocial.
Mi-do refuses to sign the agreement.
It's really stressing me out.
It's dragging on.
You need to persuade her.
This will hit the news and go to trial.
Then so be it.
Are you crazy? You have to stop her.
Mi-do is out of her mind.
Do you know how bad the situation is?
If she's doing this despite that,
she must have a good reason.
She can be a bit too emotional,
but when it comes to films,
she has strong convictions
or values.
She's very firm about them.
And I respect that.
So, about that.
How much does it cost to go to trial?
I have some savings accounts
maturing soon.
Thirty…
Is it expensive?
Maybe Mi-do just isn't cut out
for commercial films.
The "rising director" label
is no longer good for her.
Aside from the trial,
Mi-do is at a point in her career
where she needs to decide
which path to take.
The ceiling is seven meters high,
and the aisle is about 20 meters long.
The lighting is designed
to complement the bride's figure,
so brides are very satisfied with it.
Um…
We'll only have about 200 guests,
so this feels a bit too spacious.
Any other halls?
Oh, just a moment.
NAMGUNG, MI-DO
YEONHWARU
The first one was best,
but ten is too early.
Your relatives are coming from Yangyang.
I'm not inviting my relatives.
I don't want empty congratulations
from people I rarely even see.
Anyway, they already gave cash gifts
when Yeong-do got married.
I'm sure Mom will be fine.
What?
Midori, don't try to be considerate.
It's not like you.
What do you mean?
- I know you're doing it for me.
Since when are you so selfless?
It's weirding me out.
You've got it wrong.
I just don't want to invite relatives
because I'm a mess right now.
It's not for you.
Open it.
What is it?
FILM PRODUCTION GRANT APPLICATION
I checked, and you qualify.
You said the script you're writing
isn't big enough in scale
to be a commercial film.
They cover up to 80%
of the production costs,
and I'll invest the rest.
Here, one more thing.
INSTALLMENT SAVINGS ACCOUNT
This account matures next month.
I work for a good company
that offers a housing deposit loan
as an employee benefit.
So I'm going to invest this in you.
No, why would I accept this?
Mi-do.
I sometimes regret
quitting art like I did.
YEONUL HIGH SCHOOL
IT STARTS WITH SMALL ACTIONS
Namgung!
Namgung! Let go!
Are you crazy? Namgung!
Let go.
Are you sure you got everything?
I searched Mom's room and hers
and brought everything.
Why? Is something missing?
Where is it?
Where's the drawing I did for you
at the picnic this spring?
It's mine.
You drew it, but it's mine.
Hey.
What are you…
No, don't!
Hey, no!
Stop.
- Let go.
No, don't!
No!
Hey, don't do it.
No.
No, no!
No!
Do you have to do this?
Do you really have to…
You're the one hurting more.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
It's really…
over.
It's really, really…
I don't know why
I was so extreme back then.
As if keeping one drawing was a huge deal.
Funny, right?
No.
It's not funny at all.
Are you mad?
Namgung.
Do you want to draw again?
I just…
never saw it through,
so I think about it sometimes.
You said you regret it.
- Yes.
So I don't want you to end up like me.
Don't let your circumstances
make you give up what you love.
Do what you enjoy
for the rest of your life.
That suits you.
I'm starving.
Eat up.
- Okay.
Midori.
- Yes?
Open the glove box.
The theaters are all booked this year.
You always dreamed of
getting proposed to at Seoul Art Cinema.
I actually had everything
planned out last time.
What?
I couldn't put it off anymore.
Let's keep it simple today,
and I'll redo it at the theater next year.
You better act surprised
even if you already know.
Hey, Sister Lee.
Shouldn't you act more touched right now?
Or shed some tears?
How much longer
are you going to be so down?
Just give me a second, then.
Shouldn't we at least hug?
Right. Come here.
There we go.
And kiss?
- I guess so.
Hold on.
Coming.
- Okay.
Let's do it at home.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Nobu Film met
Director Kim Jung-man yesterday.
What should we do? Start working?
This bastard!
25TH
ANY SPARE MONEY?
I NEED TWO MILLION WON MORE THIS MONTH.
SIM HAE-JU
I think Director Lee is dead.
Check if she's alive.
Just a moment.
Her last social media login
was four minutes ago.
The IP is from her usual coffee shop.
So she is alive!
But she's been ignoring
all my calls and texts.
Unbelievable.
Send me her location. No, wait.
Send her location in 15 minutes.
What? How am I supposed to--
Seriously.
She must be at her usual coffee shop.
She used her card eight minutes ago.
You know the address, right?
Hey.
Lawyers talk too much,
whether in the US or Korea.
They called it a conference,
but it was practically a debate.
I barely made my flight, too.
If I missed it, I'd be divorced.
Assemblyman Kang's
book launch was today, right?
My father-in-law… What was it last time?
Hanmaeum or Saemaeum?
Anyway,
he was so mad
I missed the party members' sports day.
I just showed my face
and used the trial as an excuse to leave.
Did you see my email? About Jisang.
Yes, I saw it.
The evidence of tech similarity
that Line submitted is too solid.
The patent infringement is undeniable.
Unless something changes,
Jisang has no chance of winning.
I suggest you don't take it.
Really?
You think we'd lose?
Based on the current evidence,
yes, I think so.
That's great.
Lose the case.
Jisang's Chairman Ko and Assemblyman Shin
are clashing over the land in Daewon-dong.
If Jisang loses,
they'll need the settlement money.
So they'll sell the land.
Make it as flashy as possible,
and lose the case.
You can do that, right?
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
Come back as a director?
What? Can you not handle it?
You said you could.
I'm curious
why you changed your mind
in just a few days.
There must be something
that you're hiding.
Is that your way of saying no?
Is it your boyfriend again?
I knew it. It is.
What is it?
He won't marry you
unless you're a director?
Did he say no?
Not him. Me.
I say no.
I'd be a burden to him like this.
I'm saying no to that.
So I'm compromising.
I'll get the other candidates
out of your way,
but your history with Ms. Song?
You have to resolve that.
I know.
If we use her affair with Mr. Seo,
we could persuade her for now--
No, I don't want that.
Neither do I.
Don't give her the upper hand.
Ms. Song
is at her Gapyeong house right now.
I'll let her know you're coming.
Go there and do whatever you can,
whether it's begging or pleading.
I'm making this clear.
Persuading Ms. Song is your job.
You're early.
Oh, yes.
Are you prepared?
To deal with someone so difficult.
There might be yelling
or even violence.
I'll try to talk things out
so that won't happen.
With some people, that's impossible.
I know, but still.
With someone
who can't even use the bathroom alone?
It'll be hard.
By the way,
you have experience, right?
You just look so young.
I'm sorry, is this an interview?
Aren't you here
for the 3 p.m. caregiver interview?
No, I'm actually here
to see Ms. Song Hae-na.
Are you a reporter, by any chance?
No, I'm not a reporter…
Hae-na?
THE EMPEROR'S BLUEPRINT
What is this?
I prepared a Plan B just in case.
It's a movie K4 Pictures is preparing.
It's based on a true story.
THE CONFESSION OF THE ULTIMATE FRAUDSTER,
SONG GI-PAL
I've set it up
so you can direct this movie.
This guy…
That's right.
30,000 victims
and 50 billion won in damages at the time.
ATTRACTED INVESTORS
BY PROMISING HIGH RETURNS
He ran Korea's first mega-Ponzi scheme.
Song Gi-pal, the real estate scammer.
It was my second year with the company.
The O-SweeTato Chips started sticking
in the final process…
Mr. Namgung. Are you coming?
The moisture variance was so bad
that the whole line almost stopped.
That's when I figured it out.
It was the temperature
and discharge speed.
And thanks to that, you were the first
among your fellow hires to get promoted.
You need to be more precise.
- I think I know
why you told me to secure
all of last year's
subcontractor goods receipts.
Come on, Assistant Manager Gung
broke that.
Now, it was my fourth year.
Out of all my peers
and seniors…
- Where are we now?
Year four, the history
of his challenges and hardships.
Yes, right.
Hey, are you even listening?
We're all listening.
Kang's scheme ruined the survey.
Then? I'm dying to know
even though I've heard it before.
Right?
Out of all--
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Scheming to plot and rule.
Grill some kimchi.
- Put some kimchi on.
Right now?
- Yes.
Want some garlic?
- Yes, please.
I'll check right away.
Jeez!
You scared me.
You're looking for volume mismatches
and the tipping point.
Right? Aren't you?
Please, tell me. Am I right?
Yes, you are.
- Yes!
Right on! Yes!
Well…
It's exactly as I thought.
Checking the farm shipment records,
the unit price curve
drops at a weird point,
so it's a volume issue.
Anyway, why didn't you text me back?
If I didn't know you were busy,
I'd think you ignored me.
I almost took it the wrong way.
I did ignore you on purpose.
Right? I thought you were ignoring…
What?
I thought it'd be
more polite to tell you in person.
I don't think I can do it.
What? Why all of a sudden…
Can I…
ask you why?
I just…
suddenly lost interest.
That's a lie.
Honestly, I was motivated that day.
I was fired up with a sense of justice.
But after thinking about it…
I got scared.
Life isn't like dramas.
It's not Hanzawa Naoki.
Do you know what my dream is?
To hold out as General Manager
until I'm 60,
and then retire.
Pretty pathetic and lame, right?
But…
that's my dream.
So stop trying to sway me.
Kiddo!
Put it on my card.
It is your card.
- Oh, is it?
Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
You're welcome. Take care.
- You too.
I called a cab.
- Okay.
I'll take Manager Eom home.
And Ms. Park?
- She's in the restroom.
Manager Eom spilled stew on her.
Hold on, we'll head out first.
All right.
- Take care.
Yes, sir.
Yes, that's right. It's the Mercedes.
Yes, I'll head over there now.
Come on, get closer.
It's cold.
RESTROOM
Su-a, are you in there?
The stain on my clothes isn't coming out.
You can go ahead.
It's fine. I'll wait.
Will you be long?
I'm fine, really! You can go!
Are you sure?
I'm leaving, then.
Why do you sound like that?
Su-a.
There's only one key. What should we do?
Call the police first.
- Okay.
You want to see her die?
I have a knife!
So what?
I'll kill you first.
Don't come closer!
She's really going to die.
I'm not messing around.
I'll stab her.
Hey.
The police will be here in two minutes.
If you drop the knife and leave right now,
I won't come after you.
But…
if you try anything stupid?
Then you're dead.
What's it going to be?
We don't have time. Decide fast.
Bullshit! How can I trust you?
One minute left.
The police are coming.
Are you okay?
Stay here for a second.
No!
He has a knife.
Explain what happened.
You said you wanted
to return to directing.
That's why I gave you
a card to play against Song Hae-na.
If that's what it is, I already have one.
I know.
But using that
would be exhausting for both of us.
That's why you haven't used it,
and went to see her instead.
Wow.
What?
Doubling the settlement is fine,
but this weighs too heavily
on your conscience?
Is that it?
Oh well, then.
I'll just have to do it for you.
Hello, Ms. Song.
Director Lee visited you
at your Gapyeong house today, right?
It seems she heard it from Reporter Oh.
She actually just came to see me
and demanded her return as director.
ACTRESS SONG HAE-NA
What should we do?
Tell her I'll give her anything.
Her return, money, whatever.
Tell her I'll give her
whatever she asks for.
So please…
Mr. Han.
I'm sorry about last time.
I'll never do that again.
If this gets out, I'm dead.
Do you know how hard I worked to get here?
Of course, I know.
You can't lose everything
because of your father.
I really love acting.
I love it so much.
Stop crying, Ms. Song.
Why are you crying over this?
I'll take care of everything.
Thank you so much, Mr. Han.
First, I'll get in touch with Director Lee
and call you back.
Is this funny to you?
I'm not a psychopath.
I have my own struggles.
You called, sir?
Yes.
Bring over a Ravello 4500
and a fruit platter for her.
Also, some sparkling water and ice.
Make sure she has plenty.
Yes, I'll prepare that right away, sir.
Plenty.
I'll give you two hours.
I hope you take it seriously
and make the right choice for yourself.
What's wrong with you?
What if I had just left?
You should've screamed for help!
Are you stupid?
What about you?
You could've called the police.
Why break the door and step in?
You almost got hurt, too.
And you'd have blamed me for it!
I'd thought it all out.
I factored in the police ETA.
Unlike you, I handle crises well.
Oh, is that why
you went after someone who had a knife?
I had him.
You cost me the Civilian Heroism Award.
How selfish of me! My apologies.
Hey!
- What?
You…
Are you hurt?
Took you long enough.
I'm fine.
Are you traumatized at all?
I don't think so, for now.
Are you in shock?
I was scared earlier, but I'm fine now.
Need calming medicine?
No, I don't.
Follow me.
Come on!
Where are we going?
PRIME ON CONVENIENCE STORE
I'm over these.
NATURAL HONEY DRINK - BANANA MILK
It's not for you.
Your brain might deny it,
but you were definitely shaken up.
I'm highly resilient.
I took a test. I'm in the top 10%.
Besides, I've been an outcast
since elementary school.
I've been through worse.
I've seen it all.
Nothing too serious.
My gym clothes got stolen,
my textbooks were scribbled on…
I get it. You can stop.
I'll pretend I didn't hear it, so drop it.
Did you see the guy's face?
Without the mask, too?
Yes.
Tell me what he looked like.
Describe any distinct features.
Um…
He had a slim face overall,
with a slightly prominent chin.
Oh, he had an underbite.
Slow down.
He had an underbite…
with a prominent chin.
What about his eyes?
Nothing special about his eyes.
His features were kind of close together…
What else?
Oh, a mole!
He had a mole on his forehead.
Hey, you're hurt.
Oh.
- Jeez.
Hey, how on earth did you stop them?
I was sure they'd appeal.
He's not the type to let things go easily.
That's a trade secret.
You're something else.
This is why I can't let you go.
Okay, on that note,
let me pour you a drink.
Do you know her?
I'm sorry. I'll escort her out.
Oh.
Get out right now.
I went to beg Song Hae-na today.
I wanted to plead with her
so I could direct again.
As you said, I didn't want
to embarrass myself any further.
I felt like it was my last chance.
Okay, let's discuss this outside.
But you ruined everything.
What the hell?
Bring that bitch back here!
Right now. What the hell?
Damn it.
Are you crazy?
Do you know what you just did?
Yes, I know.
You got screwed over.
And I'm on my way
to screw you over even more.
Why?
Are you going to meet with Mr. Seo
and self-destruct?
Since when did you care about Song Hae-na?
It's funny coming from the person
who blackmailed her.
I know I'm trash.
Thanks to you, I snapped out of it.
Thank you.
Didn't you hear Song Hae-na earlier?
She'll let you come back.
She'll do whatever you want!
So what's the problem?
He'll hate it.
If he finds out what I did,
he'll hate it and be disappointed.
I don't want that.
It's your boyfriend.
Your weakness.
It's not pathetic.
Your dream.
It's cool.
It's really, really cool.
Why didn't I realize sooner?
You gave me so many clues.
I was too slow to catch on.
Since you call me trash anyway,
I'll be straight with you.
If you don't delete those photos
from the cloud today,
starting tomorrow, your boyfriend
won't be able to show his face at work.
And his future career?
It'll be ruined.
Why? Because I'll make sure of it.
You…
Wait.
Are you crazy?
What are you--
Go right ahead if you want to die.
If you mess with him,
I will kill you.
I'm not joking.
I will seriously kill you.
Now I'm really curious.
Honestly, until a minute ago,
I was just trying to scare you.
But I changed my mind.
Maybe I should mess with him.
I think it would be fun.
You bastard!
Namgung.
So don't feel too bad.
It's not pathetic.
Lots of people dream of that life.
It's snowing.
You know what?
Haemado…
is prettier in winter than in summer.
Especially when it snows like this…
it's even prettier.
How pretty.
You're awake.
What?
Why am I here?
Answer the phone first.
I think it's your boyfriend.
DIRECTOR LEE MI-DO
I guessed right.
It is your boyfriend.
QUEENS HAIR SALON
It's the first snow.
Do you really not want to see me?
I'm sorry.
I know I was wrong.
Mi-do.
Why are you out here? It's cold.
Your face is freezing.
How could you go to work now?
They'd fire me if I didn't.
I barely got the ten days off.
I want to beat you up so badly right now.
I really want to punch you,
but I'm so mad that I can't.
I'm sorry.
Hit me. I'll let you.
Damn it, you…
Did it hurt a lot?
Yes.
It hurt like hell.
Does it hurt anywhere else?
No, I'm fine.
Even the doctor was shocked
by my recovery speed.
Apparently,
if you only have one kidney left,
it grows and takes over
up to 80% of the workload.
I'm tall, you know.
My kidney will grow a lot, too.
Don't worry.
Why did you do it?
Because the peaches were so sweet.
The peaches…
were just so…
sweet.
I guess you still have
more to take from me.
You ruined my credit
as soon as I became an adult.
Was drowning me
in loan shark debt not enough?
And you want what now?
Just live like this until you die.
I don't care at all.
I went to Mr. Kim's and stole these.
Good, right?
Yes, it's good.
Do you feel better?
It's all better, right?
Yes, I think I'm all better.
You're the best, Mom.
Those peaches I had…
were just so damn sweet.
If I knew they'd cost so much…
I shouldn't have eaten them.
Right?
That was the first time
I saw Namgung Ho cry.
From the day we met at seven years old
until we turned 29,
Namgung Ho never cried in front of me.
But that night he cried in my arms
for the first time.
He cried like a seven-year-old.
THANK YOU TO CHOI HEE-JIN
FOR HER SPECIAL APPEARANCE
Once you leave,
will we never see each other again?
I'm telling you, nothing happened.
If you ever come across Park Su-a,
don't you dare talk to her.
Let's go.
You're still looking beautiful, Mom.
How have you been?
It'd still be better
to pay it back together with Mi-do.
How long have you been paying her?
Do you think I came here
to catch Song Hae-na?
You don't want to direct, do you?
You're scared, aren't you?
Subtitle translation by Cayle Kim